jimmybeanswool.com 2018-10-05

# Privacy Policy at Jimmy Beans Wool

| 

Jimmy Beans Wool takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn about our privacy policy. 

If you have questions or suggestions, please contact us. 

Last Updated: 6/4/2018 

|  This Privacy Policy explains how information about you is collected, used and disclosed by JimmyBeansWool.com and Jimmys Wool, LLC ("Jimmy Beans Wool" or "we"). This Privacy Policy applies to information we collect when you use our website and other online products and services (collectively, the "Services"), JimmyBeansWool.com, or when you otherwise interact with us. This policy does not apply to products or services with separate privacy policies that do not incorporate this Privacy Policy. We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make changes, we will notify you by revising the date at the top of the policy and, in some cases, we may provide you with additional notice (such as adding a statement to our homepage or sending you a notification). We encourage you to review the Privacy Policy whenever you access the Services or otherwise interact with us to stay informed about our information practices and the ways you can help protect your privacy. For information about the choices we offer in connection with our information practices, please see "Your Choices" below.   
---  
  
## Information Collection  
  
#### Information You Provide to Us  
  
  * We collect information you provide directly to us. For example, we collect information when you create an account, update your profile, post a review, participate in any interactive features of the Services, fill out a form or survey, participate in a contest or promotion, make a purchase, communicate with us via third party social media sites, request customer support or otherwise communicate with us. The types of information we may collect include your name, password, email address, social media user names and handles, postal address, phone number, gender, interests, preferences, payment information and any other information you choose to provide.

#### Information We Collect Automatically When You Use the Services  
  
When you use our Services, we automatically collect certain information, including: 

  * Transaction Information: We collect information in connection with each transaction you engage in via the Services, including product details, purchase price, and other transaction details. This information includes contact details (e.g., name, address, email, telephone number) so we can process your purchases. 
  * Log Information: We collect log information in connection with your use of the Services, including the type of browser you use, access times, pages viewed, your IP address and the page you visited before navigating to our Services.
  * Location Information: We may collect the approximate location of your device based the device's IP address.
  * Information Collected by Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies: We use various technologies to collect information from the computer or device you use to access our Services, including cookies and web beacons. Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive or in device memory that help us see which areas and features of our Services are popular and count visits. Web beacons are electronic images that may be used in our Services or emails and help deliver cookies, count visits and understand usage and campaign effectiveness. We do not alter or change your experience, or otherwise respond to, "DNT" or "do not track" signals.
  * We do not collect personal details such as date of birth, education, or nationality.

#### Information We Collect From Other Sources  
  
  * We may also obtain information from other sources. For example, we may collect information about you from other users, such as individuals who send you a gift through our Services, and from social networks in accordance with their authorization procedures. 

## Use of Information  
  
We may use information about you for various purposes, including to: 

  * Provide, maintain and improve our Services.
  * Provide and deliver the products and services you request, process transactions and send you related information, including confirmations and invoices.
  * Send you technical notices, updates, security alerts and support and administrative messages.
  * Respond to your comments, questions and requests and provide customer service.
  * Communicate with you about products, services, offers, promotions, rewards, and events and other news and information we think will be of interest to you.
  * Monitor and analyze trends, usage and activities in connection with our Services.
  * Detect, investigate and prevent fraudulent transactions and other illegal activities and protect the rights and property of Jimmy Beans Wool and others.
  * Personalize our Services, including by providing advertisements, content or features we think will be of interest to you.
  * Facilitate contests, sweepstakes and promotions and process and deliver entries and rewards.
  * Work with our third-party service providers who provide services such as website hosting, payment processing services, email delivery, credit card processing, auditing and other similar services.
  * Carry out any other purpose described to you at the time the information is collected.

## Sharing of Information  
  
We may share information about you as follows or as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy: 

  * We do not share your information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes.
  * When you participate in interactive features on our Services, information about you may be displayed publicly on our Services and on other sites or online services, including your photos, videos, posts, product feedback, and other information you choose to provide.
  * In response to a request for information if we believe disclosure is in accordance with, or required by, any applicable law, regulation or legal process.
  * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Jimmy Beans Wool's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.
  * We transfer information about you if Jimmy Beans Wool is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Jimmy Beans Wool will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 
  * With your consent or at your direction.

We may also share aggregated or de-identified information.   
  
## Social Sharing Features  
  
  * The Services may offer social sharing features and other integrated tools (such as the Facebook "Like" button), which let you share actions you take on our Services with other media, and vice versa. Your use of such features enables the sharing of information with your friends or the public, depending on the settings you establish with the entity that provides the social sharing feature. For more information about the purpose and scope of data collection and processing in connection with social sharing features, please visit the privacy policies of the entities that provide these features.

## Security  
  
  * We use reasonable security measures designed to protect information about you from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. As a matter of policy, we do not disclose details regarding our security measures as this could be beneficial information to criminals and other bad actors.
  * Please be advised that no security safeguards or standards are guaranteed to provide 100% security. You should always use appropriate self-protection measures and practice safe browsing on all websites.

## Advertising and Analytics Services Provided by Others  
  
  * We may allow others to provide analytics services and serve you advertisements on our behalf. These entities may use cookies, web beacons, device identifiers and other technologies to collect information about your use of the Services and other websites and apps with this device or other devices. The information collected includes your IP address, web browser, mobile network information, pages viewed, time spent on pages or in apps, links clicked and conversion information. This information may be used by Jimmy Beans Wool and others to, among other things, analyze and track data, determine the popularity of certain content, deliver advertising and content targeted to your interests to this device and other devices via the Services and other websites and apps, and better understand your online activity with our Services. For more information about interest-based ads, or to opt out of having your web browsing information used for behavioral advertising purposes, please visit www.aboutads.info/choices. Your device may also include a feature that allows you to opt out of having certain information collected through apps used for behavioral advertising purposes.
  * We may also work with other websites or platforms (such as Facebook) to serve ads to you as part of a customized campaign. Please refer to the settings of those other websites or platforms for information about any choices they offer in connection with the delivery of interest-based ads.
  * If you would like to opt out of our transmission of advertising and analytics services, please email us at [support@JimmyBeansWool.com](mailto:support@JimmyBeansWool.com).

## Transfer of Information to the U.S. and Other Countries  
  
  * Jimmy Beans Wool is based in the United States and the information we collect is governed by U.S. law. By accessing or using the Services or otherwise providing information to us, you consent to the processing, transfer and storage of information in and to the U.S. and other countries, where you may not have the same rights and protections as you do under local law.

## Your Choices  
  
#### Account Information  
  
  * You may update the online account information you provide to us by logging into your online account.

#### Cookies  
  
  * Most web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually choose to set your browser to remove or reject browser cookies. Please note that if you choose to remove or reject cookies, this could affect the availability and functionality of our Services.

#### Opt-Out of Sharing for Direct Marketing Purposes  
  
  * California's "Shine the Light" law, Civil Code section 1798.83, requires certain businesses to respond to requests from California customers asking about businesses' practices related to disclosing personal information to third parties for the third parties' direct marketing purposes. Alternatively, such businesses may have in place a policy not to disclose personal information of customers to third parties for the third parties' direct marketing purposes if the customer has exercised an option to opt-out of such information-sharing. If you wish to opt-out of our sharing of your information with third parties for the third parties' direct marketing purposes offline, please follow the instructions in Sections 8 below. 
  * We do not share your personal information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes.

#### Receiving electronic communications from us  
  
  * You may opt out of receiving promotional emails on a going-forward basis from one of our Services by following the instructions in those emails or by changing the preferences through your online account with each Service. If you opt out, we may still send you non-promotional emails, such as those about your account or our ongoing business relations.
  * If you have provided your information to Jimmy Beans Wool, and opt-out, Jimmy Beans Wool will put in place processes to honor your request. This may entail keeping some information for the purpose of remembering that you have opted-out.
  * If you have an account, you can [log in to your account](https://www.jimmybeanswool.com/secure-html/onlineec/accountLogin.asp) and edit your personal options. These changes are effective on the site immediately.
  * If you don't have an account, you can [update your notification options](https://www.jimmybeanswool.com/notificationsUpdate.asp) for all of our email lists. These changes are effective on the site immediately.
  * You can request that we delete your personal information by contacting us. Please include your name and order number, if the order number is available.

#### Promotional Calls  
  
  * You may opt out of receiving promotional calls from us by letting us know during one of those calls or by sending an email to [support@JimmyBeansWool.com](mailto:support@JimmyBeansWool.com) with the subject line "opt out to calls".

## How to access, correct, delete or exercise other rights regarding your Personal Information  
  
  * Where applicable law allows for such a request, if you would like to request to access, correct, object to the use, restrict or delete Personal Information that you have previously provided to us, or if you would like to request to receive an electronic copy of your Personal Information for purposes of transmitting it to another company (to the extent this right to data portability is provided to you by applicable law), you may contact Jimmy Beans Wool at [support@JimmyBeansWool.com](mailto:support@JimmyBeansWool.com) with the subject line "Data Subject Request." We will respond to your request consistent with applicable law.
  * For your protection, we may only implement requests with respect to the Personal Information associated with the particular email address that you use to send us your request, and we may need to verify your identity before implementing your request. We will try to comply with your request as soon as reasonably practicable. 
  * Please note that we may need to retain certain information for recordkeeping purposes and/or to complete any transactions that you began prior to requesting a change or deletion (e.g., when you make a purchase or enter a promotion, you may not be able to change or delete the Personal Information provided until after the completion of such purchase or promotion). There may also be residual information that will remain within our databases and other records, which will not be removed.

## Additional Disclosures  
  
  * Our website may provide links to other Internet sites, content or videos (embedded or direct links) maintained by third parties. We are not responsible for the sites, content, or videos accessed via the links, and we have not reviewed the privacy practices of those third parties. We encourage you to review the privacy practices of any such third parties.
  * We do not knowingly request or collect personal information from any person under 13 years of age without prior verifiable parental consent. If you believe that your child under the age of 13 has submitted personal information to us in connection with our website without prior verifiable parental consent, please contact us at support@JimmyBeansWool.com so that we can take steps to delete the personal information that she or he provided.
  * If you are an international customer and you provide personal information through our website, you agree that the personal information will be transferred to and processed in the United States of America and any other country or jurisdiction at our sole discretion. The laws that apply to the use and protection of personal information in the United States or other countries or jurisdictions in which we transfer or process personal information may be different than the laws and protections in your country.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy  
  
  * Jimmy Beans Wool may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by placing a notice on our site or by contacting you directly.

## Contact Us  
  
  * If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at: 4850 Joule St Ste A1, Reno, NV 89502, [support@JimmyBeansWool.com](mailto:support@JimmyBeansWool.com), or (775)827-9276.
